# 大家好 好多粉絲問我們那個送終雞去哪裡啦
Hi everyone! Many fans asked us where the “Rooster the Final Respect” has gone.
(Note: Rooster the Final Respect, translit: "song zhong ji" is a pun, homonym to Song Joong-ki in Mandarin)
# 其實在我家哦 我藏在我家啦
It’s at home with me, in fact. I hide it at home.
(Note: Rooster the Final Respect, translit: "song zhong ji" is a pun, homonym to Song Joong-ki in Mandarin)
# 要不然那 被那個狗啊 它老是 那個狗老是喜歡追它
Otherwise, the, it’s always, the dogs, the dogs always like chasing after it.
# 如果我們不在的話那個狗就把它吃了
It would just be eaten by the dogs if we're not there.
# 所以我把它藏在這裡面
That’s why I hide it here inside.
# 你看 被我抓啦 這個 就這個公雞
Look! It’s in my hands now. This one, it’s this rooster.
# 現在都好大啦 好老啊
It’s very big, very old now.
# 不叫了
It’s not yelping.
# 叫啊 叫啊 以前就咕咕咕的叫 現在不叫啦 哎呦
C’mon! Yelp! It used to yelp like “gu gu gu”. But it doesn’t yelp now. Ayo!
# 抓都不住你了
I can’t even hold you.
# 你看這它個
Have a look at its,
# (這個 這個叫甚麼)
this one. How is it called?
# (這個叫??)
It’s called wattle.
# 不動聲色 你看
It’s a statue. Look!
# 它的嘴巴這裡 很利的哦 看到沒有 啄一下
Its beak is here. It’s really sharp! See? If you got pecked,
# 肉都會啄掉一塊
a whole piece of flesh might got pecked off.
# 現在它活的好滋潤啦
It’s now having a well fulfilled life.
# 它天天跟 跟一群母雞混在一起
Every day, it mingles with a whole herd of hens.
# 滿臉紅光
It’s face is bright and red.
# 現在差不多有五六斤吧 這個小
I think it’s around three kilograms now. It’s so small.
# 這公雞長到十斤都可以長 你看它指甲 看到沒有
This kind of roosters can grow up to five kilograms. Have a look at its nails, see?
# 它這個指甲好長啦
Its nails are really long.
# 它這個老公雞就這樣子的
This is rather typical for old roosters like this one.
# 快兩年啦
It’s almost two years old now.
# 你看 那個就是閹雞來的 那個就被閹了
Look! That one is a capon. It has been neutered.
# 好 把你放走啦
Alright! I let you go.
# 咕咕咕咕咕 打架 來
Gu gu gu gu gu! C’mon! Fight!
# 它們不打
They don’t fight.
# 這個閹過的哦 閹過的漂亮點 看到沒有
This one is a capon, you know. Capons look prettier, see?
# 油光發亮的
It’s so shiny.